schoolpassage.com 2014-05-17

# Privacy Policy « The Online Degree Guide is here to help you on your quest of finding the right degree program and college for you.

## [Privacy Policy ](http://www.schoolpassage.com/privacy/)

Protecting your privacy is important to us. We hope the following information will help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us on our site.

Personal Information  
The definition of “personal information” in context to this privacy notice refers to any information that you give out that may disclose part or your whole identity. We will only gather personal information that you decide to offer us, such as email addresses. We are committed to our no spam policy and will not sell any information collected from our visitors.

We only apply the personal information that you submit to us for their intended purposes. We do not share personally identifiable information with third party websites, organizations or other persons without your consent unless it is:

1\. Necessary to provide you with a requested service;  
2\. Lawfully authorized or required;  
3\. Or utilized in the prevention or minimization of a serious and immediate threat to a party’s health.

Legal Disclaimer  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

Collection of Information  
As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information Includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp and click Stream data. This Information collected will be used to research, analyze and evaluate trends and content featured on the website, to order to improve the services to our consumers. Website traffic, that is non-identifiable by person, is used in our data collection. We may use your IP address to assist in the diagnosis and administration of our website operations. It may also be utilized in the gathering of demographic data. Occasionally, we and other websites referred to may uses cookies.

Cookies  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. See “Third Party Advertisers & Links.” This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by this website only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. [See the “Third Party Advertisers” section.]

Third Party Advertisers & Links  
Our websites contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each website to which we may link that may collect personally identifiable information. While we may use cookies in some parts of our website, cookies received with advertisements on our website are collected by the respective advertising companies, and we do not possess access to or control of such information gathered.

Your Rights  
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by emailing us or by postal mail at the contact information listed below. In protection of the privacy of yourself and others, we may have to acquire identification evidence before we can allow you to access to information regarding you in order to retrieve or change it.

Change in customer internet privacy statement  
From time to time we may revise its Privacy Policy if we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, either by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. Please check back periodically for any updates.
